connected yo mr. Mishimoto here today
we're going to be looking at the Cena
prism tube and some other setup stuff I
got on my helmet so yeah if you guys
liked the video see if it comes up if
not how not dislike button speech there
comes a point in every motorcyclists
life where he or she wants to enjoy
watching themselves ride through that
really cool trail or cash that priceless
moment of their friends failing in the
funniest way when our moment comes
well so does the hunt the hunt for the
best cheapest action camera if you've
seen any videos on this channel or know
of any of the big names in moto vlogging
like do it with Dan well terrific and
arson rise did you know it's at least
possible to record what you do at any
given moment with all that being said
I'm almost certain GoPro came to your
mind GoPro is no doubt a popular choice
when it comes to action camera
unfortunately the price of one of these
high demanding cameras is far greater
than most modern browsers starting out
can afford but I have good news there
are other companies like Sony ion and
contour that produce similar products
for a cheaper price tag the action
camera that stuck out most to me and
more of an immortal blogging community
is the Cena prism - with a built-in
helmet microphone and very helpful voice
prompting software that lets you know
what your camera is doing at all times
no more checking to see if your red
light is on the scene in prism tube also
has a super low profile when it comes to
mounting on your helmet easily making
this one of the biggest selling features
in my opinion the adjustable ball mount
allows for easy movement and sturdy
maneuverability the camera also shoots
at 1080p at 30 frames a second which in
my opinion is all one needs in terms of
quality content one of the best things
about this camera is that it's only 120
US dollars easily the most simple and
affordable action camera on the market
today connected
[Music]